Guide to the Lewis L. Delafield, Eugene D. Hawkins and Affiliated Attorneys Records circa 1856-1921 (bulk, 1880s-1910) MS 157
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Boxes labeled H-D (Hawkins-Delafield), circa 1853-1924 (bulk 1880s-1910)
  - H-D Bundles #48-65, circa 1874-1899 (Offsite-box 58)
    50) Charles Hyde & Son agreements with New Orleans & Northwestern Railway Company and others, ca. 1897-98.
    51) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist]
    52) John Chester v. Tomas W. Willets, ca. 1883.
    53) Thomas J. Fay v. J.I. Case Threshing Machine Co., Kings County, ca. 1899.
    54) Edward M. Kerr v. Tomas W. Willets et al, ca. 1884-91.
    55) Henry C. Lester v. Ozro W. Clapp and Dwight O. Clapp (Clapp & Co.), ca. 1897.
    56) Matter re: Department of Docks and James Bigler & Co, ca. 1874.
    57) Caroline Neff v. Charles H. Hammett, Charles L. Hyde, et al, Kings County, ca. 1894-98.
    58) Printed material only re: West India Company.
    59) Thomas F. Bushey v. Ozro W. Clapp and Dwight O. Clapp (Clapp & Co.), ca. 1894.
    60) Commercial Telegraph & Messenger Company matters, ca. 1893.
    61) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist]
    62) Theodore H. Price, William G. McCormick, Ralph M. Stuart Wortley (Price, McCormick & Co.) v. Andrew M. Lowenthal, ca. 1896.
    63) Automatic Bank Punch Company v. James Brady, John Newton Williams, et al, ca. 1888-91.
    64) Alfred N. Beadleston v. Eugene D. Hawkins, executor of Dexter A. Hawkins estate, and James Worden Gedney as surviving partner of Hawkins & Gedney, ca. 1887.
    65) Francis S. Kinney v. Constance E. Gianotti et al, ca. 1893.
  - H-D Bundles #67-94, circa 1874-1897 (Offsite-box 59)
    67) Seven insurance policies on Hawkins property, 1880s.
    68) Theodore H. Price, et al v. Samuel Mayer, ca. 1893.
    69) Harry Heeb jr (infant) v. Brooklyn Heights Railroad Company, ca. 1897.
    70) Patrick Harnett v. Long Island Railroad Company, ca. 1891.
    71) Protest of property owners on Vesey Street between Broadway and Church Street against extension of 3rd Ave Railroad Company through Vesey, ca. 1888.
    72) Freling H. Smith (assignee of Owens & Mercer) v. Charles W. Allen, Kings County, ca. 1885.
    73) Theodore F. Taylor v. Wilson Godfrey, ca. 1887.
    74) Settlement of account of Charles E. Lydecker as administrator for estates of Charles Cody, Annie Cody (infant), and Mary Ann Green (or Cody), ca. 1892.
    75) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist]
    76) Automatic Bank Punch Company v. Brady Manufacturing Company, Williams Check Punch Company, et al, ca. 1888.
    77) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist]
    78) Charles W. Allen v. Arthur Sterz, ca. 1895.
    79) Property title for C.W. Luyster, 32 West 60th Street, ca. 1890.
    81) Mary J. Moran (executrix of Edward G. Moran estate) v. New York Elevated Railroad Company & Manhattan Railway Company et al, ca. 1894.
    82) H.H. Upham, John Tully, Louis I. Haber v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company, Manhattan Railway Company, et al, ca. 1892.
    83) Matters re: National Dredging Company, Atlantic Dredging Company, etc., ca. 1892.
    84) A.B. Barton v. William Windom, Minnesota district courts, ca. 1886.
    85) Arthur Tooth et al v. Max Bleiman, ca. 1893.
    86) Meredith Howland (executor of Gardiner G. Howland estate) v. Louisa Howland Clendenin, Joanna Howland Grinnell, et al, ca. 1892.
    87) Charles W. Millard v. Charles L. Hyde, Charles H. Hammett, and Livingston E. Davison, ca. 1896-97.
    88) Edward Skillin (administrator of Simeon D. Skillin estate) v. Connecticut Mutual life Insurance Company, and related re: Daniel Titus, Annie M. Titus, ca. 1886.
    89) Albert V. Meeks et al (executor of Joseph W. Meeks estate) v. Metropolitan Elevated Railway Compamy and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1877-1890.
    90) City of Ironwood v. William E. Coffin, et al, ca. 1897.
    91) Sophie Mayer v. T. Judson Kilpatrick and James M. Stewart, ca. 1893.
    92) Wilson Godfrey v. Theodore F. Taylor, Charles C. Murphey and Washington McLean, ca. 1885.
    93) Matter re: assignment of Stephen L. Merchant and Frances W.G. Bellows to John C. Maben, ca. 1879.
    94) James Bigler et al v. Commissioners of New York City Dept of Docks, ca. 1874.
  - H-D Bundles #95-116, circa 1886-1899 (Offsite-box 60)
    95) Matter of Nelson H. Salisbury as assignee of Joseph W. Duryea (accounts, etc.), ca. 1895.
    96) T. Judson Kilpatrick et al v. John Selfridge, ca. 1893.
    97) Caroline Converse v. New York Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1892.
    98) Samuel T. Hubbard Jr et al v. John[?] F. Bowdon, ca. 1897.
    99.1) Various agreements re: James H. Goodsell, including with Hawkins and with The Spectator Company and with Technics Publishing Company, ca. 1892.
    99.2) Settlement of accounts of Sarah A. Meeks and Edwin D. Meeks as executors of Albert V. Meeks estate, ca. 1894.
    100) Harry Heeb Jr (infant) v. Brooklyn Heights Railroad Company and other matters re: Heeb, ca. 1896.
    101) Francis S. Kinney v. James B. Kinney et al, ca. 1893.
    102) Wilson Godfrey and Ralph E. Sumner v. the canal boat "Thomas King" et al, U.S. District Court, Southern Dist of New York, ca. 1887.
    103) Mabel de Forest by her guardian Charles E. Wilson v Camilla L. Edwards (executor of Walter Edwards estate) et al, ca. 1895.
    104) Walter L. Carter v. Ozro W. Clapp and Dwight O. Clapp (Clapp & Co.), ca. 1897.
    105) Davenport Malt and Grain Company v. Max Blumenthal, ca. 1895.
    106 and 108) Malcolm Baxter Jr v Ozro W. Clapp and Dwight O. Clapp (Clapp & Co.), ca 1897.
    107) Isabella B. Jones v. New York Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1894.
    109) John P. Schenger v. New York Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1898-99.
    110) Henry C. Lester v. Ozro W. Clapp and Dwight O. Clapp (Clapp & Co.), ca. 1897.
    111) Robert A. Sharkey v. American National Telephone Company, ca. 1892.
    112) William W. Waterhouse v. Esther J. Jennings, Annie B. Jennings and Walter Jennings, ca. 1896.
    113) Agreements re: Washington Hadley, Anne W. Hadley, Anna Willets, Mary Willets, etc., ca. 1886.
    114) Charles L. Hyde v. Alfred H. Harrison, ca. 1893.
    115) Harry Bates Jr v. August Strassburg, U.S. District Court, Southern Dist of New York, ca. 1889.
    116) Thomas P. Ivy and James S. Ivy (doing business as Ivy Brothers) v. Golden Stock Telegraph Co., ca. 1889.
  - H-D Bundles #117-151, circa 1886-1900 (Offsite-box 61)
    117?) John P. Schenger v. Metropolitan Elevated Railway Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1897-98.
    118) Automatic Bank Punch Company v. William S. Williams, ca. 1890.
    119?) Mary J. Moran (executrix of Edward G. Moran estate) v. New York Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, re: complaint about impact on property of rail operation, ca. 1893-94.
    120) Samuel T. Hubbard, Theodore H. Price, Walter C. Hubbard, Frederick W. Dillingham and Ralph N.S. Wortley v. Benjamin S. Hoskins, ca. 1895.
    121) Matter re: estate of Augusta S. De Forest, ca. 1887.
    122) Arthur Tooth et al v. Max Bleiman, ca. 1898-99.
    123) Correspondence re: Mary E. Downs v. Charlotte E. Taylor, ca. 1894.
    124) Samuel T. Hubbard et al v. Daniel Mayer and Louis J. Crine, ca. 1893.
    125) City of Ironwood matter, ca. 1894.
    126) Thomas C. Evans v. Thomas H.S. Hamersly, ca. 1886-88.
    127) Agreements re: Charles Toppan, De Witt Smith and Aranias F. Smith, ca. 1894.
    128) Charles W. Allen v. Joseph C. Clayton, ca. 1892.
    129) Elizabeth Ironside v. Charles N. Ironside et al re: William Higgins and Maria Higgins estates, et al, ca. 1892.
    130) Ambrose P. Gaines v. Theodore H. Price, ca. 1900.
    131) Agreement between LaMontagne, Clarke & Co, E.M. Fulton Jr, McElroy & Gibert, and Eliot Norton, ca. 1894.
    132) Home Soap Company corporate matters, ca. 1898.
    133) Samuel T. Hubbard Jr et al v. Jacob Lorch, ca. 1894.
    134) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist, ca. 1892.]
    135) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist].
    136) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist, ca. 1898.]
    137) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist].
    139) Bigler v. Duryea; and Salisbury v. Bigler, ca. 1896.
    141) Mary A. Berman v. Samuel T. Hubbard et al, ca. 1894-99.
    142) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist].
    143) Phoenix Babcock et al v. Martin F. Collins et al and Minneapolis Improvement Company Northeast, Minnesota Supreme Court, ca. 1894.
    144) John Morton v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1891.
    145) Malcolm C. Anderson v. Arthur E. Bateman, ca. 1898.
    146) John D. Dent v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company, Manhattan Railway Company, et al. Also Dent v. Sarah K. Cowdin as trustee under will of Elliott G. Cowdin, ca. 1892-99.
    147) Samuel T. Hubbard Jr v. George O. Cox et al, ca. 1895.
    148) Second Congregational Unitarian Church agreement, ca. 1894.
    149) Exchange Publishing Company v. L. Breckinridge Cabell; and also v. Leroy Davidson), ca. 1894.
    150) Frances S. Brown and Elizabeth A. Brown v. Theodore R. Chapman et al, ca. 1886.
    151) Frank T. Day v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company et al, ca. 1892.
  - H-D Bundles #152-171, circa 1884-1907 (Offsite-box 63)
    152) Accounts of William V. Negus (administrator of Emma L. Nones estate), ca. 1899.
    153) Matter re: estate of Francis M. Babcock, Anoka County, Minnesota, ca. 1892. The matter seems to also concern the Goodsells and Spectator Company.
    154) Frederick Hill v. William Dalton Mann, ca. 1884.
    155) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist].
    156) Matters re: American National Telephone Company, ca. 1886-89.
    157) William F. Deakyne v. J. Daniel Eby, ca. 1895.
    158?) Bulk holds People of the State of New York on the relation of Mabel V. Price v. William H. Maxwell (New York City school superintendent), et al re: licensing of graduates from the Normal College of New York as public school teachers, ca. 1903-05. There is also a packet with a few documents re: Mary E. Gilroy (administratrix of Annie B. Gilroy estate) v. Andrew Mullen, ca. 1907.
    159) Settlement of account of Alfred Heritage, executor of Joseph N. Scott estate, ca. 1889.
    161) Theodore H. Price, William G. McCormick, Ralph M. Stuart-Wortley (firm of Price, McCormick & Co) v. Robert P. Saunders, ca. 1897.
    162) Theodore H. Price to German Exchange Bank matter, ca. 1889.
    163) Settlement of account of Shepherd Knapp and Edward S. Knapp as executors of Gideon L. Knapp estate, ca. 1886.
    164) Samuel T. Hubbard Jr et al v. Daniel Mayer, Louis J. Crine, Morris Mayer, and Jacob Lorch, ca. 1894.
    165) Traders National Bank v. Charles M. Blaisdell et al, ca. 1893.
    166) Louis P. Prout v. August C. Hockemeyer, ca. 1888.
    167) Re: Waterlou collection of claims, correspondence, ca. 1884.
    168) National Central Bank of Cherry Valley, New York v. Max Blumenthal and C&L Heidenheimer (corporation), ca. 1898.
    169) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist]
    170) Cassius C. Ball v. Ozro W. Clapp and Dwight O. Clapp (Clapp & Co.), ca. 1897.
    171) William W. Sharp and Charles S. Bryan et al v. James D. Stevens and Louise R. Stevens, ca. 1985.
  - H-D Bundles #172-186, circa 1862-1890s (Offsite-box 64)
    172) Ambrose B. Burbank v. John B. Manning, ca. 1895.
    173) Max Blumenthal v. C&L Heidenheimer (corporation), ca. 1896-97.
    174?) William W. Johnson v. C.A. Baldwin Co.
    175) Various loose papers. Most seem to relate to Dexter A. Hawkins matters, though not all (e.g. papers re: Brumley), 1862-1895. Also Dexter Hawkins's 2 inch metal stamp which appears to read as New York City and State's Commissioner for Massachusetts.
    177) Various matters including M.F. Wills, et al v. Toppan Manufacturing Company, Dexter Hawkins matters, etc., ca. 1870s-90s.
    178) At least 3 matters here: Ira A. Miller v. Emmet C. Gibson; will of Theodore H. Price; and Ball-Warren Commission Company v. James D. Stevens, ca. 1897.
    179) Various small matters: Max Blumethal; Ryan v. Cranston; Louise de F. Cock will.
    181) Miscellaneous matters.
    184) James Bigler v. Justin McCarthy, 1890s.
    There are other miscellaneous unnumbered packets or individual loose documents from the original H-D box labeled as #180-186. Some matters noted: Claim of Mrs. Goodsell on Spectator Company; Ralph E. Sumner v. Matthew H. Gregory et al, Queens County, ca. 1892; estate of Augusta M. Knapp; Southerly agreement on parchment, 1870; Louis A. Green v. Louisville, New Albany & Chicago Railway Company; Francis Gordon Brown title abstract for Avenue A at 86th Street; James Bigler matters; Dexter Hawkins "personal matters," and many more.
  - H-D Bundles #187-212, 1870s-1902 (Offsite-box 65)
    187) Packet of "Miscellaneous matters."
    188) Stuyvesant Fire Insurance Company corporate matters, ca. 1900.
    189) James Colgate and Retsof Mining Company matters, ca. 1894.
    190) Application of Julia M. Phyfe as executrix of James D. Phyfe estate, ca. 1892.
    191) George Crocker v. Samuel D. Davis and Charles B. Van Nostrand, ca. 1898.
    192) Application for appointment of a Committee of the person and property of Joseph G. Creamer, an alleged insane person, ca. 1897.
    193) Edward H. Perkins v. Theodore H. Price, et al, ca. 1896.
    195) Title abtract to George Keister for 146 West 34th St., ca. 1892.
    197) Theodore H. Price et al v. Akron Printing & Publishing Company, et al, ca. 1899.
    198) Application of Price, McCormick & Co. re: certificate of stock of the New York Ontario and Western Railway Company, ca. 1897.
    199) Correspondence re: Fanny Ann Pirie (of Aberdeen, Scotland) matters with William Bradford and Isaac Heilbrunn (of Brooklyn), ca. 1896.
    200) Edwin B. Meeks (executor of Joseph W. Meeks estate) v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1890.
    202) William H. Roe v. Ida Coster Williams, ca. 1902; Application of William Plimley (Commissioner of Jurors) for enforcement of fine on Theodore H. Price (delinquent juror).
    203) Michael McCullough v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company, et al, ca. 1894.
    204) T. Judson Kilpatrick matters: Hadley Pulp Company corporate matters, ca. 1889; title abstracts and other property matters re: William Schomp and others, ca. 1892.
    205) Dexter A. Hawkins v. Francis Gordon Brown, ca. 1883.
    206) Dexter A. Hawkins: various personal matters: correspondence, etc. on political matters, political reform, re: New Central Coal Company (Hawkins is on the company's Executive Committee), and other matters, 1870s-80s.
    207) Edwin B. Meeks (executor of Joseph W. Meeks estate v. Charles De Rham, et al, ca. 1890.
    208) Settlement of accounts of Edwin B. Meeks (executor of Joseph W. Meeks estate), ca. 1892.
    209) Palmer Campbell (receiver) v. Robert Easton Erwin et al, ca. 1893.
    210) Application of Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company relative to acquiring title (in re: Jones et al), ca. 1890.
    211) Protest of Edwin B. Weeks (executor) to Board of New York City Tax Commissioners, ca. 1886.
    212) Application of William Alexander Smith as executor of George Jones estate to sell real property (and related), ca. 1896.
  - H-D Bundles #213-224, 231, 232, circa 1872-1901 (Offsite-box 66)
    213) Various patent-related matters and agreements concerning Wilhelm Pickhardt, Adolf Kuttroff and James H. Stebbins Jr, ca. 1874-1890. Title abstract to Pickhardt for property on 15th Street between Irving Place and 3rd Avenue.
    214) Accounts of Joseph W. Meeks, John Meeks, and William H. Meeks as executors of Joseph Meeks estate, Suffolk County, ca. 1872.
    215) Meeks estate matters, ca. 1873-1884.
    217) Sophia T. Meeks estate matters, ca. 1895.
    218) Various matters (leases, agreements, mortgages) concerning various Meekses (Sarah A., Edwin B., Albert V., etc) and their estates, Suffolk County, ca. 1885-92.
    219) Theodore H. Price, et al v. George Conkling, ca. 1897.
    220) Accounts of Edwin B. Meeks (executor of Joseph W. Meeks estate).
    221) Various matters: Wilson Godfrey indenture with Evelyn B. Hamlin (and related), ca. 1885-1886; Drew v. Rooke, 1901; Partnership between T. Judson Kilpatrick and James M. Stewart, 1891; and partnership among Schuyler E. Brumley, Richard Corbett, Alida Brumley, Hiram L. Brumley, 1881.
    222) United States v. Joseph Willets et al, U.S. District Court, Southern Dist of New York, ca. 1877. Also a small bundle re: indenture between Alfred N. Beadleston et al and William C. Dornin, 1888; and printed material re: Mary Day v. New York Elevated Railroad Company, et al.
    223) Bulk of this bundle is Aaron A. Fishel and Abraham I. Adler (firm of Fishel, Adler & Schwartz) v. Lorillard Spencer; and vs. Vickery & Hill Company. Both matters in U.S. District Court, Southern Dist of New York, ca. 1895-97. There is also a packet within #223 of James Bigler v. New York City Dept of Docks matter, ca. 1874.
    224) American Bell Telephone Company et al v. Samuel T. Hubbard Jr et al; and also Mary Schondorff, executor v. Max Stiner, ca. 1901.
    231) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist].
    232) Thick roll of what appears to be office-related expense invoices, ca. 1898.
  - H-D Bundles #225-230, circa 1889-1898 (Offsite-box 67)
    225) Patrick Skelly v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1895. There are also several indentures here, ca. 1889, a couple with Skelly's name and so may be related.
    227A & B) H.B. Claflin Company v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1898.
    230A & B) Various matters concerning Isaac Edward Garvey (mostly), Louis Leubuscher, James Duane Livingston, People's Gas Light and Coke Company, ca. 1898.
  - H-D Bundles #233-248, circa 1867-1904 (Offsite-box 68)
    233) A loose pile of papers on various matters. Some indications of content: Palestine Market House Association of Palestine, Texas matter, ca. 1877; Surveys, plans, etc re: Gunnison Steel & Iron Company of Colorado; Papers of William H. Wadsworth re: government claims and Masonic certificates left with Robert Sturgis; George Ahrens and James A. Scrymser matters, including re: Aurora, Elgin & Chicago Railway Company, ca. 1901; William G. Mccrea v. The Mutual Bank, ca. 1904; Copies of wills of Rufus and Edward Delafield and other Delafield/Prime family documents; and more, overall circa 1870s-1904.
    233A) Daniel Mooney v. New York Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1896; Carlos D. Siegert et al v. Max Stiner, ca. 1902.
    234) Ellen O'Connors v. Marcus Kramer et al, ca. 1902.
    236) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist].
    237) Jane Aldrich Moore will and probate, ca. 1890.
    238) Various property maps, at least some re: Sutphen's lots on 72nd and 73rd streets (a/k/a Boggs Estate), ca. 1867. Likely others not identified by the archivist.
    239) William L. Breyfogle agreements.
    240) Property-related documents re: Edwin Meeks, ca. 1874.
    241) Luncheon Club corporate matters, ca. 1898.
    242) Small bundle re: Theodore H. Price and will of Martha W. Watkins, ca. 1900.
    243) Annie R. Prime, guardian of Charlotte H. Prime (infant) v. Neuville O. Fanning, ca. 1900.
    243A) Matters Re: Germania Savings Bank and Ralph G.M.S. Wortley and Charles F. Buck, ca. 1901.
    243B) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist].
    245) Willard Richards v. Andrew P. Morison, ca. 1900.
    246) Mark Harris v. Theodore H. Price et al, Erie County, ca. 1900.
    247) George R. Fearing et al v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, concerning at least in part the Trinity Building, ca. 1900.
    248) James F. Mack v. Charles C. Miller, ca. 1900.
  - H-D Bundles #250-253, 255A, circa 1897-1901 (Offsite-box 69)
    250A) Theodore H. Price et al v. Charles E. Trice et al, ca. 1900.
    250B) Small pack of documents that appears to be another Price matter.
    251A) Mary E. Beadleston v. Richard S. Newcomb.
    251B) Envelope with a few documents re: L. Delos Mansfield: Nyack waterfront property.
    251C) Claim of Firemans Trust Insurance Company v. Shade & Co in bankruptcy (small packet).
    251D) Matter of assignment of Price, McCormick & Co for the benefit of creditors re: disputed claim of John H. Dunne, ca. 1901.
    252A) A Robert Sturgis matter concerning Knight Neftel re: payment disputes or delays in connection with a Decorating Fund, ca. 1897-98.
    252B) John S. Martin v. Manhattan Railway Company, et al, ca. 1898.
    253A) Matter of appraisal of property of William Powell Mason, deceased, ca. 1901.
    253B) Annie R. Prime v. N.O. Fanning.
    255A) George Crocker v. Manhattan Life Insurance Company, ca. 1900.
  - H-D Bundles #254-260, circa 1874-1906 (Offsite-box 70)
    254A) Matter re: application of Harlem River & Portchester Railroad Company and the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad Company for a writ of certiorari, ca. 1899.
    254B) Theodore H. Price, William G. McCormick, Ralph M. Stuart-Wortley (firm of Price, McCormick & Co) v. Frederick A. Burnham, ca. 1896.
    255B) William G. McCrea v. The Mutual Bank, ca. 1906.
    257) Edward H. Myers, at al v. Clinton P. Paine (bankers Paine & McLaren), et al, ca. 1896.
    258) Julia M. Phyfe (executrix) v. Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1894.
    259A & B) David Boyd as administrator (of Samuel Boyd estate?) v. Robert Boyd, Raphael Monaco, Eloise Miller, and Raphael Viliano, ca. 1874-1894.
    260A) New York Life Insurance and Trust Company v. James A. Benedict et al, ca. 1902.
    260B) Matter of appraisal of property of Anne S. Faulknor, deceased, ca. 1901.
    260C) Matter of appraisal of property of Charles L. Young, deceased, ca. 1902.
  - H-D Bundles #264, circa 1901 (Offsite-box 71)
    Entire box holds multiple bundles numbered 264, all concerning the matter of the application of Price, McCormick & Co. (the firm comprised of partners Theodore H. Price, Ralph G.M. Stuart-Wortley and William G. McCormick) for the benefit of creditors. Includes claim of George Crocker and perhaps others, ca. 1901.
  - H-D Bundles #265-267, 269-274, circa 1890-1908 (Offsite-box 72)
    265) Herbert Germond et al as executors of Wellington Gerond estate v. New York Elevated Railroad Company, Manhattan Railway Company, et al, ca. 1902.
    266?) Acadia Canal Company (Louisiana) corporate matters, ca. 1900-1901. Also relates to the Abbott-Duson Canal Company.
    266B) Agnes E. Tracy v. Abraham L.A. Himmelwright, ca. 1903.
    267) Mary Day v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1898; also Henry S. Day v. Metropolitan Elevated Railroad Company, Manhattan Railway Company, et al, ca. 1890.
    269) Peter Marie v. George Crocker re: terminating tenant leases at 72 & 74 Broadway and at 9 & 13 New Street, ca. 1898.
    270) [Small bundle with few documents, not identified by archivist].
    272) James F. Mack v. Charles C. Miller, ca. 1900-03.
    273) Auguste Richard and Margaret Richard to Elvine Richard, deed of trust, ca. 1904.
    274) Louise Hartshorne Leeds will, 1908.
  - H-D Bundles #268, 275-285, circa 1902-1904 (Offsite-box 73)
    268) Maria Bentz v. Harold Hartshorne, ca. 1902.
    275 & 285) American Peroxide & Chemical Company matter, ca. 1904.
    276) Agreement between Jarvis & Co and Metropolitan Finance Company, 1902.
    277) Louise Hartshorne Leeds bond to Willam P. Beaver and Ellen B. Beaver, ca. 1902.